<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?><News><!-- NewsEntry Start -->
<NewsEntry>
<Date>09/11/2011</Date>
<Title>Giselle Monteiro On Cover Of Maxim India September 2011 Issue</Title>
<Body>
Giselle Monteiro is being featured on the cover of September 2011 edition of Maxim India . The photos will be part of the Maxim India September 2011 edition.
</Body>
</NewsEntry>
<!-- NewsEntry End --><!-- NewsEntry Start -->
<NewsEntry>
<Date>03/04/2011</Date>
<Title>Abhishek Bachchan To Rap In Dum Maaro Dum</Title>
<Body>
Abhishek Bachchan will after 6 years once again rap in his upcoming movie Dum Maaro Dum (2011). Last time Abhishek was rapping in front of a microphone was in movie Bluffmaster (2006) . Dum Maaro Dum also stars Bipasha Basu, Aditya Pancholi, Rana Daggubati, Prateik Babbar, with special appearance in an item song Deepika Padukone . The movie is being directed by Rohan Sippy and is scheduled for release April 22, 2011.
</Body>
</NewsEntry>
<!-- NewsEntry End -->
<!-- NewsEntry Start -->
<NewsEntry>
<Date>03/01/2011</Date>
<Title>Salman Khan And Asin Thottumkal In Ready</Title>
<Body>
Salman Khan is currently shooting for his next movie Ready (2011) starring Asin Thottumkal being directed by Anees Bazmee with music from Pritam. The movie is a family drame due to release in June 2011. The director is well known for making movies that he can see with his family and hence they should be entertaining to all.
</Body>
</NewsEntry>
<!-- NewsEntry End -->
<!-- NewsEntry Start -->
<NewsEntry>
<Date>02/21/2011</Date>
<Title>Sushant Singh Rajput Wants To Leave Jhalak Dikhhla Jaa</Title>
<Body>
Sushant Singh Rajput, plays the role of Manav on Pavitra Rishta who is currently also a contestants on Jhalak Dikhhla Jaa Season 4 wants to quit the dance reality show due to a back injury. Sushant has been one of the best dancers on the show along with his choreographer Shampa, getting good scores and is the favorite to win the title this year. Last week on the show requested that he be allowed to quit the show becuase he is unable to perform.
</Body>
</NewsEntry>
<!-- NewsEntry End -->
</News>