<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?><News><!-- NewsEntry Start --><NewsEntry><Date>7/12/2010</Date><Title>Katrina Kaif To Perform Song As A Belly Dancer</Title><Body>Katrina Kaif will be performing a song in which she will be dancing like a belly dancer. The song will be choreographed by Farah Khan for her movie Tees Maar Khan (2010) , which stars Akshay Kumar , Akshaye Khanna , and Deepika Padukone . The director also mentioned that Katrina will be learning the dance to ensure the item number is done justice. Katrina is currently busy shooting for Zoya Akthar’s Zindagi Milegi Na Dobara (2010).</Body></NewsEntry><!-- NewsEntry End --><!-- NewsEntry Start --><NewsEntry><Date>07/10/2010</Date><Title>Hrithik Roshan Wax Figure In Madame Tussauds London</Title><Body>Bollywood star Hrithik Roshan will join Amitabh Bachchan , Salman Khan and Aishwarya Rai Bachchan as the next Bollywood actor to have his wax figure at the famous Madame Tussauds in London. Hrithik is currently in Spain shooting for his next film, Zindagi Milegi Na Dobara (2010). Shahrukh Khan 's wax figure was the first one for a Bollywood star in the Madame Tussauds in Los Angeles.</Body></NewsEntry><!-- NewsEntry End --><!-- NewsEntry Start --><NewsEntry><Date>02/25/2010</Date><Title>Tendulkar: Little Master, writes history</Title><Body>Sachin Tendulkar , the little master entered the records books once again becoming the first cricketer to score a double century in a 50 over international OID, in India's victory over South Africa in Gwalior. The previous record was held by Saeed Anwar's 194 against India and Charles Coventry's 194 versus Bangladesh. One Day International cricket, started in 1971 had to wait 4 decades to witness this great achievement. His unforgettable unbeaten 200 came off just 147 balls with 25 fours and three sixes in it in front of the crowd at Captain Roop Singh Stadium.</Body></NewsEntry><!-- NewsEntry End --><!-- NewsEntry Start --><NewsEntry><Date>02/10/2010</Date><Title>Deepika Padukone On Cover Of Maxim India February 2010 Issue </Title><Body>Deepika Padukone is being featured on the cover of February 2010 edition of Maxim India . The photos will be part of the Maxim India February 2010 edition.</Body></NewsEntry><!-- NewsEntry End --><!-- NewsEntry Start --><NewsEntry><Date>01/26/2010</Date><Title>Supermodel Padma Lakshmi Beats Aishwarya Rai and Freida Pinto </Title><Body>Supermodel Padma Lakshmi, has grabbed the 15th and Lakshmi Menon has moved into the 45th position on the Askmen.com top 99 women poll leaving behind Aishwarya Rai Bachchan at number 50th and Freida Pinto 63rd. The number one stop was taken by Canadian actress Emmanuelle Chriqui, while Penelope Cruz took the 7th spot and "Tranformers" star Megan Fox the 11th spot.</Body></NewsEntry><!-- NewsEntry End --></News>