<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<rss version="0.91">
	 <channel>
	 
	    <title>
		   BollywoodMovies.us : Latest News About Bollywood Movies
		</title>
		
		<link>
		   http://www.bollywoodmovies.us
		</link>

		<description>
		   We provided the latest Bollywood Movie News, Photo/Picture gallery, Wallpaper of all the Bollywood movie Actor/Actress.
		</description>
		
		<language>en-us</language>
		<lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2006 12:00:00 EST</lastBuildDate>
		
		<item>
		   <title>
		   		  BollywoodMovies.us : Latest News About Bollywood Movies
   		   </title>
		
		   <description>
		   		   We provided the latest Bollywood Movie News, Photo/Picture gallery, Wallpaper of all the Bollywood movie Actor/Actress.
		   </description>

		   <link>
		   		   http://www.bollywoodmovies.us
		   </link>
		   
		   <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2005 12:00:00 EST</pubDate>

		</item>
		
		<item>
		   <title>
		   		  BollywoodMovies.us : Actress Photo and Picture Gallery Added
   		   </title>
		
		   <description>
		   		   We have recently added the photo and picture gallery for the following actresses, Aishwarya Rai, bipasha basu, kareena kapoor, 
				   katrina kaif, mallika sherawat, namrata shirodkar, preity zinta, priyanka chopra, rani mukherjee, sonali bendre, sushmita sen, and tanushree dutta.
				   Also added picture gallery for India Tennis Star Sanai Mirza.
		   </description>

		   <link>
		   		   http://www.bollywoodmovies.us
		   </link>
		   
		   <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2005 12:00:00 EST</pubDate>

		</item>
		
		<item>
		   <title>
		   		  BollywoodMovies.us : Aishwarya opts out of yet another movie.
   		   </title>
		
		   <description>
		   		   Aishwarya's busy schedule has forced her to not be able to work on Rajkumar Santoshis Saamna , starring Ajay Devgan , Akshay Kumar and Nana Patekar. Her last release with Rajkumar Santoshi was Khakee with Amitabh Bachchan and Akshay Kumar . Ash is currently shooting for Umrao Jaan in Jaipur.				    
		   </description>

		   <link>
		   		   http://www.bollywoodmovies.us
		   </link>
		   
		   <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2006 12:00:00 EST</pubDate>

		</item>
		
		<item>
		   <title>
		   		  BollywoodMovies.us : Bollywood Forthcomings Movies 2006
   		   </title>
		
		   <description>
		   		   Bollywood is ready to role out many new movies this coming year, Producers have a lot of money invested in big Bollywood ventures and hope the audience comes out to the threaters to watch the movies. One of the first big release of year 2006 is Raj Kumar Santoshi's Family starring Amitabh Bachchan , Akshay Kumar , and Bhumika Chawla release in January. Eklavya , another Amitabh Bachchan movie, will be release in January. Rang De Basanti , starring Aamir Khan is also scheduled to be released in January. Shahrukh Khan stars, Happy New Year and Farhan Akhtar's Don are to also schedule to release thereafter.				    
		   </description>

		   <link>
		   		   http://www.bollywoodmovies.us
		   </link>
		   
		   <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2006 12:00:00 EST</pubDate>

		</item>

		<item>
		   <title>
		   		  BollywoodMovies.us : Father and Son Duo to together again
   		   </title>
		
		   <description>
		   		   The father and son combination of Amitabh Bachchan and Abhishek Bachchan has proved successful in recent times. Their charisma in Sarkar and Bunty Aur Babli has lead to great success for those movies. Bunty Aur Babli has done really well at the box office and Sarkar is being made out to be one of the best of the senior Bachchan. Now Karan Johar is banking on the father-son duo in his next movie, Kabhi Alvida Na Kehna , slated to be released in the summer of 2006. Other stars that are being metioned with the movie are Shahrukh Khan , Preity Zinta and Rani Mukherjee. 				    
		   </description>

		   <link>
		   		   http://www.bollywoodmovies.us
		   </link>
		   
		   <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2006 12:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		</item>

		<item>
		   <title>
		   		  BollywoodMovies.us : Priyanka to appear in Maxim 
   		   </title>
		
		   <description>
		   		   Priyanka to appear in Maxim Date: 01/03/2006 Priyanka Chopra has been selected to appear on the cover, in a red revealing outfit, of the first international men's lifestyle magazine to enter India, Maxim. The magazine is available in major Indian cities, including Delhi, Mumbai, Kolkata, Chennai and Bangalore and will provide information on celebrities, sports, movies and the auto industry. .  				    
		   </description>

		   <link>
		   		   http://www.bollywoodmovies.us
		   </link>
		   
		   <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2006 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		</item>

		<item>
		   <title>
		   		  BollywoodMovies.us : Aishwarya Rai in the top 10 of the E! 101 Sexy Bodies list 
   		   </title>
		
		   <description>
		   		   Aishwarya Rai in the top 10 of the E! 101 Sexy Bodies list Date: 01/03/06 Aishwarya Rai is starting 2006 the same way she started 2005, she has made the elite list of 101 sexiest bodies put together by TV channel E!, it was impressive to make the into the list, but it's more impressive since she beat out Hollywood names like Halle Berry, Jessica Simpson, Britney Spears and Madonna to end up in the top 10. Others on the list include Beyonce Knowles, Angelina Jolie, and Brad Becks.  				    
		   </description>

		   <link>
		   		   http://www.bollywoodmovies.us
		   </link>
		   
		   <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2006 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		</item>

		<item>
		   <title>
		   		  BollywoodMovies.us : Amitabh and Rani get Screen awards for Black
   		   </title>
		
		   <description>
		   		   Amitabh Bachchan and Rani Mukherjee received the best actor and best actress awards at the Hero Honda 12th Annual Star Screen Awards respectively. Amitabh was also nominated for best supporting actor for his role of DCP Dashrath Singh in Bunty Aur Babli whom is starred opposite his son Abhishek Bachchan , who collected the award on his father's behalf. Abhishek Bachchan himself picked up 2 awards, best actor in a comic role in Bunty Aur Babli and Jodi No.1. Black won all together 10 awards out of the 12 categories it was nominated for including best film and best director for Bhansali.  				    
		   </description>

		   <link>
		   		   http://www.bollywoodmovies.us
		   </link>
		   
		   <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2006 12:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		</item>

		<item>
		   <title>
		   		  BollywoodMovies.us : Kareena Kapoor and Shahid Kapur together
   		   </title>
		
		   <description>
		   		   Kareena Kapoor and Shahid Kapoor have signed the next film of Priyadarshan's, titled Chup Chup Ke . They are also working together on 2 other films, Boney Kapoor's Milenge Milenge and Subhash Ghai's 36 China Town .  				    
		   </description>

		   <link>
		   		   http://www.bollywoodmovies.us
		   </link>
		   
		   <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2006 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		</item>

		<item>
		   <title>
		   		  BollywoodMovies.us : Sexy Goswami in Aksar
   		   </title>
		
		   <description>
		   		   Udita Goswami career started her in sexy roles being part of the Bhatt camp. Her sexy role reappeared in other such movies as Paap and Zeher. But her role in Aksar is published as even more sexy then her past movies. The promos have her intense lip locking scenes with smooch king Imraan Hashmi.  				    
		   </description>

		   <link>
		   		   http://www.bollywoodmovies.us
		   </link>
		   
		   <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2006 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		</item>

		<item>
		   <title>
		   		  BollywoodMovies.us : Abhishek Bachchan and Aishwarya Rai on screen chemistry
   		   </title>
		
		   <description>
		   		   Abhishek Bachchan and Aishwarya Rai on screen chemistry is great as it can be seen in the now famous song, Kajra Re, of the movie Bunty Aur Babli. They have also worked together in the past in Na Kaho and Dhai Akshar Prem Ke, which did not have much box office success. Let's see what 2006 bring for both the stars, it would be great to see the onscreen chemistry become sometime off screen, only time will tell.  				    
		   </description>

		   <link>
		   		   http://www.bollywoodmovies.us
		   </link>
		   
		   <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2006 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		</item>

	 </channel> 
</rss>